(Gablehouser:)We're hoping to have him
do graduate work here.
- Graduate work, very impressive.
- And he's only 15 years old.
(Sheldon:)Not bad.
I myself started graduate school at 14.
(Dennis:)Well, I lost a year while my family
was tunneling out of North Korea.
(Leonard:)Advantage, Kim.
(Gablehouser:)I thought maybe you
could show Dennis around.
(Gablehouser:)Let him see why we're the best
physics research facility in the country.
I know you're not.
(Dennis:)You don't have an Open Science Grid
computer or a free electron laser.
(Dennis:)The string theory research
being done is a dead end.
(Sheldon:)Excuse me, that is my research,
and it is by no means a dead end.
(Dennis:)Well, obviously, you don't see it yet,
but trust me, you will.
Dennis, we've discussed this.
(Gablehouser:)We're in the process
of updating our equipment.
(Gablehouser:)We welcome your input
on our research goals.
We agree to look the other way
if you use 20 percent...
...of the money you attract to smuggle
your grandfather out of Pyongyang.
(Gablehouser:)We want him here, boys.
(Gablehouser:)- Make it happen.
- Yes, sir.
(Sheldon:)You can count on us. We're on it.
What the hell do you mean, "dead end"?
(Dennis:)I mean, the whole landscape
of false vacuums in string theory...
(Dennis:)...could be as large
as 10 to the 500th power.
(Dennis:)In addition...
(Dennis:)Ooh, look, chocolate milk.
(Sheldon:)I sense a disturbance in the force.
[IMITATING YODA]
A bad feeling I have about this. Mm.